听力考试正式开始。
现在请看听力选择部分。
第一题，请听录音中八组短对话，
每组对话后有一个小题
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出与对话内容相符的图片，或能回答所给问题的最佳答案。
每组对话读两遍。
Number one. Wow, so many fresh strawberries!
Yes, I picked them this morning.
Number two. We should do something to protect the environment.
That's true. I ride my bike to school every day.
Number three. Excuse me, is there a around here?
Um, yes. Go along this street and turn left at the first crossing.
Then you'll find it.
Thank you very much.
Number three. Excuse me, is there a library around here?
Um, yes. Go along this street and turn left at the first crossing.
Then you'll find it.
Thank you very much.
Number four. Alan always has a good way to do things.
Yes, he is the most creative person I know.
Number five. It's so hot, I'd like to have a cold drink.
What about you?
Why not? Thank you.
Number five. It's so hot, I'd like to have a cold drink.
What about you?
Why not? Thank you.
Number six. Who often helps you with your study after school?
My teachers, but sometimes my parents.
What about you, Tom?
I often ask my friends for help.
Number six. Who often helps you with your study after school?
My teachers, but sometimes my parents.
What about you, Tom?
I often ask my friends for help.
Number seven. What are you doing, Alice?
I'm looking for my dog.
It's missing. Number seven.
What are you doing, Alice?
I'm looking for my dog.
It's missing. Number eight.
I don't think Amy should be allowed to do the job.
Me neither. If she can do it, anybody can.
Number eight. I don't think Amy should be allowed to do the job.
第二题，请听录音中两段较长的对话，
每段对话后有几个小题
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出能回答所给问题的最佳答案。
每段对话读两遍。
听第一段较长的对话，完成第九至第。
十一三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Hello Alice, how's your school life in America?
Well, I didn't know it would be so difficult.
We usually study ten to eleven hours a day.
Why? Do you have many classes every day?
Not really. There are too many books to read.
If you don't read enough, you will find it hard to follow the teachers in class.
That's true. What do you usually do on weekends?
On Saturdays, I usually spend a whole day cleaning and washing clothes.
And then I often go out with friends on Sundays.
I see. Please take good care of yourself.
Thank you. Hello Alice,
how's your school life in America?
Well, I didn't know it would be so difficult.
We usually study ten to eleven hours a day.
Why? Do you have many classes every day?
Not really. There are too many books to read.
If you don't read enough, you will find it hard to follow the teachers in class.
That's true. What do you usually do on weekends?
On Saturdays, I usually spend a whole day cleaning and washing clothes.
And then I often go out with friends on Sundays.
I see. Please take good care of yourself.
Thank you. well, Jack.
听第二段较长的对话，完成第十二至第十五四个小题。
现在你有二十秒钟的时间阅读这四个小题。
What's up? I feel tired these days,
Do you sleep well?
Not really. I often wake up during the night.
Why not take more exercise,
That will help you sleep well.
Mum, I run, I go swimming and I go for long walks, so my problem isn't exercise.
Perhaps you need to see a doctor.
I don't think so.
I don't feel sick, just tired.
Well, the weather is fine today.
Let's go out and fly a kite.
Just relax. Sounds good.
Maybe being relaxed is helpful.
You don't look well, Jack.
What's up? I feel tired these days, Do you sleep well?
Not really. I often wake up during the night.
Why not take more exercise, Jack?
That will help you sleep well.
Mum, I run, I go swimming and I go for long walks, so my problem isn't exercise.
Perhaps you need to see a doctor.
I don't think so.
I don't feel sick, just tired.
Well, the weather is fine today.
Let's go out and fly a kite.
Just relax. Sounds good.
Maybe being relaxed is helpful.
请同学们翻到第七页，找到第三大题，继续做听力填词题。
第三大题：听力填词。
请听下面两则新闻，根据所听到的内容写出可以填入下表一到五。
空格处的适当单词，每空现填一词。
新闻读两遍。
现在你有三十秒钟的时间阅读表格中的相关信息。
tired. Good evening.
This is News Time.
This morning, a bear got free from a and scared people in the park.
As it's Saturday today, there were a lot of people in the park.
The police had a hard time getting it back to the zoo.
Luckily, nobody got hurt in the event.
Now, sports news.
This afternoon, the Chinese women's basketball team won the Asian Cup again after 12
years. They beat the Japanese team with a 73 -71 victory.
It was really a close game.
Now listen again.
Good evening. This is News Time.
This morning, a bear got free from a zoo and scared people in the park.
As it's Saturday today, there were a lot of people in the park.
The police had a hard time getting it back to the zoo.
Luckily, nobody got hurt in the event.
Now, sports news.
This afternoon, the Chinese women's basketball team won the Asian Cup again after 12
years. They beat the Japanese team with a 73 -71 victory.
It was really a close game.
听力测试到此结束，请将答案涂写到答题卡的相应位置，然后继续做其他
题目。